Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Ugly Ducklings@Viki
Why are you sitting there!
I'm sorry!
Hurry, hurry.
Watch it.
Episode 6
Sorry!
Oh what to do? Look at you shivering.
Are you really cold?
Should..should we go to the hospital first?
It's okay. Just go.
How can I just go?
Then shall I take you home before I go?
Just go I said.
But... How can you go alone like this?
Please..
Please just go.
I am asking you.
Yes driver. Since he's cold, please turn up the heat and
take care of him until he gets home.
Yes. Thank you.
Cooold!
Seong Joon, why aren't you coming?
Ah, I am the driver.
The customer isn't feeling well so I am taking him home right now.
What?
I'm sorry. I have to go.
- What?  - I will explain it all later.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
Ah! I got dressed up for nothing.
I should take some selfies.
I don't know his apartment number.
You're the tenant from 502
Seong Joon.
Seong Joon..
Vinegar goes in here too?
I don't know.
Hye Jin.
Oh? Seong Joon.
How's your temperature?
It's a little better.
How did you get here?
I called you and the driver told me you weren't feeling well.
Soup is almost ready. Go lay down.
You waited for a long time earlier right? I'm sorry. I suddenly felt ill.
But why did you want to see me today?
I got your jacket back from the dry cleaners so I wanted to return it to you.
I was worried that you'd go around without any clothes on.
I have so much clothes so there's no reason for me to be naked.
I told you you can give it back to me at any time.
I have a habit of quickly returning any items I've borrowed.
Hurry up and go get rest. I will let you know when it's done.
Hurry. Hurry.
Why did he do that?
The rain was pouring down and I was looking at him like this..
and he did this to me.
Maybe I looked pretty?
Do you have the princess syndrome?!
Whatever it is, he probably caught a cold. Did he take his medicine?
It would be too much to go to his apartment, right?
Yes, too much. Too much.
Should I leave it at the guard's desk? Or by Quick? (Express delivery service)
Weirdo Reporter
Yes, Reporter Kim.
What is Reporter Kim? Reporter Kim?
We're not at the office.
What is my Dongseng (younger sibling) doing while it's raining? How about some rice wine and scallion pancakes with your Orabeoni? (formally, older brother)
But right now I have something I have to take care of.
Ah. Orabeoni, can I ask a favor-
Ah..no, no. Never mind.
What is it that you're being so ambiguous and can't tell me?
Tell me, what is it?
It's just that..Seong Joon got soaked in the rain and if you could get him his medicine for me..
What?
Never mind. What am I saying right now?
Don't worry about it. I'll go myself.
What is with her? She can't even talk to her first love and she wants to bring him some porridge?
A day like this calls for some rice wine and scallion pancakes!
Even if you go, you won't hear anything pleasant, Jackson.
Damn! Ah seriously.
- Yes.  - Our Dongseng probably knows because you've experienced me before.
I am not the kind of person who runs errands for people or takes care of patients but
whose request is this? It's my dongsaeng's request.
- What?  - So I was thinking about doing a porridge run for you.
Really?
Ah! Thank you Report- I mean, Orabeoni.
Then what is that thankful dongsaeng going to do for her orabeoni?
- What?  - You've heard before, right? Give and take?
If I fulfill your request this time, you have to fulfill three of my requests in the future. Call?
What? Why do I get three?
I'm all about give and take.
If you don't want to, it's fine. It's nothing for me to feel sad about. Hanging up now.
Ah, call, call, call! I got it. I will fulfill your requests no matter what.
You say this now but are you going to act like a hostile and pretend this never happened?
This won't do. Repeat after me. 'I, Kim Hye Jin, promise to fulfill Kim Shin Hyeok's request three times, no matter what.'
Oh that's so random. An oath?
Hanging up.
'I, Kim Hye Jin, promise to fulfill Kim Shin Hyeok's request three times, no matter what.'
Amen.
Seong Joon, it's all ready.
Seong Joon.
You're asleep again.
You have to eat that before you take the medicine..
Huh? I've seen coffee shop unnies before but I've never seen a coffee shop oppa!
- Huh?  - Huh?
What is this?
You abandoned me and left earlier! What are you doing here?
I'm so sorry about earlier.
Someone who lives here had something urgent happen.
What about you Mr. Suite 2014? What brings you here?
Well, I too have someone here I know.
I have to..ugh..meet quickly about something..
Ah, about earlier, I'll explain it all to you later.
Okay. See you at the hotel.
Yes.
Five.
Mr. Deputy Chief Editor.
Deputy Chief Ji.
Ji Seong Joon?
Hey, Seong Joon!
Ah, I guess he's not here.
Then this thing. Should I leave it at the desk?
I had this with me. Open sesame.
What is this? He's here?
Ah, he's in deep sleep.
Ah!
This is that problematic puzzle or whatnot.
Listen here.
Your first love is the one who you always say
'Look Intern' to.
That Kim Hye Jin. Do you know?
Do you?
Did he buy himself the porridge?
Ah! How could food..smell like this?
Wow. A person could die from eating this.
Ah it's rancid! So rancid.
I guess he'll eat it when he feels like it.
Why is he sweating so much?
What is this?
Ah, why am I doing this?
Really..
Ah, Hye Jin!
Ah, you scared me!
You're up?
What is Reporter Kim doing here?
I came over to make sure you weren't dead.
I heard you got soaked during the rain.
Who did you-
Ah...this Intern, uselessly meddling again..
But really, did you sleep here?
Ah..Then did you think I'd sleep out in the hallway listening to the sound of cicadas?
In this cool fall air?
Even wearing my dressing gown?
Oh this underwear! It's mine!
Oh I came over in such a hurry that I forgot to pack some underwear.
- But still, how can you put on someone else's underwear? Take it off right now. - Really? Okay.
Ah, no, no. Just wear it. Have it.
Don't return it to me. Do.do..do..don't return it to me ever!
Okay. Yes! Underwear! Bonus item!
Go wash up. Let's have breakfast and go to work.
He had a party all night.
Hurry up and go wash up.
Did you catch a cold too?
Yes, maybe. I was fine until yesterday.
But you too? Did someone else catch a cold?
No-
A lot of people seem to catch it lately.
Let's see.
We're out of cold medicine. Stay here, let me go buy some.
Hey, hey. Sit down, sit down. The pharmacy isn't even open yet.
- Is it too early?  - Yeah.
Ah, then I'll pack you some fruit. Have some at work.
You have to take a lot of vitamins at times like this.
I'll get you some sesame mushroom soup after work. You eat that the cold is gone.
It's fine. I'll get over it soon.
You have to fight the cold off at the beginning of it.
Go to the hospital if you start sweating, got it?
Yes.
Dongseng's first love ate the whole bowl of porridge and is all better now.
Mission complete.
It's a relief.
I fell asleep so I didn't get to see you leave.
Thank you for the porridge. I'll call you later.
Porridge?
Well, porridge or soup.
Deputy Chief Editor you're awesome!
Did you bring it back from the U.S.? This underwear?
- Made in U.S.A.? America?  - Yes.
Maybe because it came across the ocean, it's so wearable!
By any chance, can't you give me two or so more?
Or is it something I can buy here? This underwear?
Continuing with the underwear! Underwear! Really!
Ah, really. I wish you would stop that underwear talk and that peculiar behavior too.
Eyy! Let's share the information, please.
- Please get off of me.  - Huh?
We even spent the night together. You're trying to keep your distance too much, Deputy Chief Editor.
- Come here.  - I said stop sticking to me! Seriously!
Come-
What is that cologne?
What is your cologne I said!
Come on!
What is with that combination?
Come on. How much is it?
Were they always that close?
Who cares?
Oh, Joon Woo!
- Hello.  - You were here.
You're have a subtly good sense of style.
What is that combination now?
From now on, I will stay with you.
I will be your umbrella.
♫ Just like me, they long to be ♫
- Hye Jin  ♫ close to you. ♫
Ah, good morning.
Are you feeling a little better?
Ah, well...
- Look, Intern.  - Yes?
Ah, why did you tell that Reporter Kim and make it so annoying for me?
Because of him, my apartment is like messy trash-
What are you trying to do with that bizarre face?
What to do?!
I-I'm sorry.
Ah. It's okay.
He...he..here too it splattered.
Ah, it's okay.
I said it's oka-
Ah really! I told you it's okay!
I'm sorry.
You were so determined to come up. Why haven't you gone in yet?
Perhaps, you were waiting for me?
There's no way.
It's entertaining to make fun of that one too.
Underwear..
Here, Director Cha...
Hye Jin, do you have a cold?
Hye Jin, you can't get disappointed because we have work to do.
Next week is our deadline so if we don't get it finished, we're done.
You understand our situation, right? You have to understand it.
Yes, I understand.
Ah, really everyone is just too much. Treating someone like a virus.
So Jackson, is it a cold?
Yes. I think so.
Ah! I told you to go outside!
Huh?
I told you not to do that. Here. It's bad.
Put your mask on.
Hye Jin, here.
Hye Jin.
This completed translation. Here and here, please supplement it.
Yes, I will do it.
Jackson.
Oh it's cold! What is this?
Ah, stay still.
What are you doing?
Stop getting treated like a virus and stay like that. Take your medicine too.
You're not even feeling well so how can you take care of someone else?
I'm going.
- Look, Intern!  - Yes!
Why aren't you bringing me the minutes?
We didn't have a meeting today so what minutes..?
Who asked for today's? I meant yesterday's. Yesterday.
I gave yesterday's minutes to you yesterday.
I don't think I've seen it.
Yesterday, I left it on the top of your desk.
Ah, I'll get another copy made and quickly bring it to you.
Let's work properly. Properly.
Yes.
I definitely gave him that yesterday.
What's with him? By the way, that cold medicine might make you drowsy.
If you get too sleepy, take a nap in the medical service room.
Okay?
Jackson?
Oh.
He takes care of me now that I've become his dongseng.
We're going down.
Wait for me! Deputy Chief Editor!
Deputy Chief!
What's with him?
Seriously, what is it?
What am I doing? Really?
Oh, Hye Jin.
Do you feel any better?
Thanks to you.
Thank you for last night and sorry.
Do you know the sesame mushroom soup eatery at the intersection?
Go and have lunch there later.
When I eat that there, my cold goes away.
Really?
Then let's have lunch there together later.
You made me porridge so I owe you one.
I'll pick you up at lunch time.
No.
Let's just meet there later.
Coming to my workplace is a little...you know.
Okay.
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
Oh, Hye Jin.
You're here?
Ah, it's raining all of a sudden.
I know. Is it a sudden shower?
What?
It's that..
You used to hate the rain..
Right.
But..it's okay now.
Ah.
It's a green light!
Oh! It's a go!
But, why do you always call the green light 'go'?
I call it a go because it's a go.
Then, what about the red light?
The red light?
The red light is the red light. My whole family does it.
Aren't you coming?
Oh... Yes, I'm coming.
Oh! I think there's going to be a newly-published book. There's an article.
My dear readers, I'd like to tell you that my new work is at the finishing stage.
I ask for a little more patience before we meet again soon. From, Ten
Wow, that book is probably getting released soon.
Hey, just thinking of the reviews is getting me excited.
Ah, but Sunbae. Have you heard the rumor?
Ten is supposed to be Korean.
An Ahjumma in her 40's at that.
Ahjumma in her 40's. Stop talking nonsense and hold this.
Scratch the middle of my back.
Harder. Before, everyone said that the person was French.
That JE's Guillaume or whoever.
And last year, they said it was an American,
JE's Douglas K. There was all that fuss about it. Do you remember or not?
I heard that Ten is Murakami.
That he was hiding it on purpose.
Ten is Haruki?
That's doesn't make any sense. They have totally different styles.
What do you mean, Haruki?
No one knows.
Joanne Rowling too. Once she got famous, she hid her name and published a mystery novel.
No, that's not right.
According to a reliable source, it's definitely a Korean.
An Ahjumma in her 40's at that.
Where did you find your source? Will you tell me?
Ciao!
Hello.
♫ Caro Mio Ben♫
That's it everyone. Let's get back to work.
Yes.
Huh? An onion?
Does anyone know what this onion is?
- Not sure.  - I don't know.
Ah, that's a prop we're going to use at the photo shoot.
It's an onion directly imported from Italy. It's worth 1,000,000 Won. ($1000)
What? 1,000,000 Won!?
1,000,000 Won..!
You're lying again, aren't you.
Aren't you quick. Not even a kindergartener would be that gullible. How can you fall for it?
What is this onion really? It's a mystery.
- Please sort the mail.  - Yes.
Seriously, what is this!
Yes, this is the editing office of The Most.
Ah, he's out of the office right now.
Yes.
I will leave him a message that you called.
When you catch a cold, if you keep an onion nearby,
it's been said that it can lessen the strength of the cold virus.
Then that onion from earlier is...
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Ugly Ducklings@Viki
Que bella es bella!
Our Deputy Chief Editor's pure smile, I've seen for the first time.
It was so beautiful that I took a photo without realizing.
Something good must have happened.
Perhaps you're dating?
Pardon?
Who could that woman be?
Amore mio
In gratia...
Smile? When did I smile?
This flower like smile, let me see some more in the future. Edi, Edi, Ji Deputy Chief Editor.
Why would you smile there? Why?
Don't smile.
Here, the list of sponsors.
Ddan, ddan, ddan ddan ddan.
What do you think he's doing in there?
I'm not sure.
What's wrong with me?
I'm going.
Me too.
Good job everyone. See you all tomorrow.
Bye.
Sunbae, do you have everything?
See you.
Isn't it nice?
Good job and this,
by tomorrow,
for that interview. The key points...
Ah yes.
Take care.
- Make sure you wear a mask.  - Yes.
I forgot to take the medicine.
Ah, I'm sleepy.
This cold medicine is really strong.
Ah, so sleepy.
This won't do. Let's chew gum. Gum.
Deputy Chief Editor, you haven't left yet?
It was over here somewhere..
Ah, you scared me!
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you surprised?
What do you mean surprised...surprised...For real I wasn't surprised at all. For real.
Ex... Excuse me.
What is it? Oh.
Who put my bag here?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
He's oddly acting mental today.
- Hye Jin, you're not leaving now?- Ah, I should go now.
- Let's go.- Yes.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Ugly Ducklings@Viki
Who is it?
Ah...This stupid cold! My bus!
Ahjusshi! Ahjusshi! Ahjusshi, stop!
Thank you, thank you.
Where am I?
Ahjusshi, I'm getting off!
She sleeps everywhere.
But where is this place?
Towing Service
Thank you.
Receipt
Oh sorry. It must be still morning there. I had something to ask you.
Under extreme stress, the trauma that you overcame can come back.
Don't get stressed and even if you do, take care of it right away.
It's best not to let yourself get bothered.
And someone who has nothing to do with me keeps overlapping with someone I knew from 15 years ago
but I don't know what the reason is.
And instead, the person whom I used to know feels strangely unfamiliar to me.
I keep feeling as if it's not the same person whom I used to know.
Hey, it's a given that people change after 15 years
Then did you think that someone would stay the same like they traveled through time?
The fact that you can't forget your first love, it's a form of a Zeigarnik Effect.
Zeigarnik Effect?
Zeigarnick Effect -- the tendency to remember incomplete tasks or unfinished business.
What are you doing, not coming in?
The night air is so nice and it's waking me up a little too.
Because of the cold medicine, I've been out of it all day. Why did you come out?
I was thinking of doing some exercise.
But, you got off work a little late today.
Yeah.
An Incomplete Effect would be easier to explain but,
it's a case of not being able to forget something that you never got to finish.
In the end, the fact that you can't forget your first love
might not be because you have a keen affection for her or because it's fate.
This is so weird.
You never got to see it to the end and that might be the real reason you can't easily forget her.
So get out of your past and live in the present is what I'm saying.
The management team liked leaving work right on time but
the team now works overtime almost every night.
Well, I got used to it now.
But, I heard that this team might disintegrate and The Most magazine might discontinue too.
Discontinue? Then..the magazine is entirely disappearing?
I heard it coincidentally, but there's 3 months left.
No, is there now 2 months left?
If we can't get the numbers up within that time, I think it will get discontinued.
The Editing Team will disintegrate too.
Then, what about Ji Seong Joon?
I don't know, if he doesn't have a reason any more to be here,
I'm thinking he might just go back.
I'm not too sure either.
Is our Dongseng's doing okay with her cold? Shall I give her a call?
Wait, wait. Let me have a sip.
Appetizer?
The reason for your restlessness is because of the prior 'toong'?
Is it because of that man?
Ah, what kind of a man is he that you have to lie and say that you're getting married?
A stalker?
There's just someone. A man I can't see.
Without my being aware, a man whom I keep falling for.
The more I like him, the more uneasy I become..
Someone who
I can't like.
A married man?
No!
If not, a fugitive...
a minor... Well, these days, kids develop a lot quicker.
But...still..a minor is a little bit...
Seriously, what do you think I am?
It's not like that.
If it's not, then what's the problem?
Just...
someone whom I should have stopped liking sooner.
But I didn't think I could stop it on my own so
I asked you for a favor, Mr. Suite 2014.
Then, it's not a married man, not an fugitive and not a minor.
If you like him, then keep seeing him.
You can see him.
It's not that easy.
'Love is crazy and openly allowed.'
Even in movies, there's a line like that. ( From the movie, 'Her' )
Be crazy.
Doesn't everyone love while being that crazy?
Instead of needlessly complicating it,
if you let yourself be crazy, it's simple.
Don't look back and regret it but
just go for it.
What are you looking for?
Ah, those shoes.
Now that you mention it, they were so unworn.
I thought they were thrown out by mistake so I left them with the guard.
In the end, if i have two legs, this is something that will forcibly end for me regardless of my own will.
Even if I get hurt, I want to try it.
As far as I can go, I want to go.
♫ The one whom I've been waiting for. ♫
♫ Maybe because I don't know about love, ♫
♫ I couldn't say anything ♫
♫ You were always near me ♫
♫ The one who is looking at me ♫
♫ I'm afraid you still don't know yet. ♫
♫ If I take a step, maybe you'll know me  ♫
♫ Should I try to wait a little more  ♫
♫ On my own, the love that I've started without you knowing ♫
♫ Should we do it together now ♫
♫  Maybe because you're the only one I've known  ♫
♫  I can't love anyone else  ♫
♫  My heart keeps feeling strange  ♫
Oh, about that schedule for the location scouting,
we're planning on looking near the sea in Gangwondo's Bosung where there's view of the landscape.
The concept is ' Traveling Alone'
so we're thinking about capturing a model enjoying a tranquil afternoon by the sea.
Right now, we're in the process of looking elsewhere in the Bosung area and
we just need Deputy Chief Editor to make your choice.
Deputy Chief Editor.
Yes?
About the business trip.
How is it going?
For now, it's been set for the day after tomorrow
and we've reserved the condo that our company has there.
Since you're the one in charge, you'll have to go and then
Ah Reum and I. We three can go, was what I was thinking.
I'm sorry, but can you take me out, Sunbae?
- Why?  - There's an omission with the pictorial
so I think we'll have to do a supplementary shoot.
Seol, you should go in my place.
Me?
Ah, I already have so much to do..
Why don't we send Kim Hye Jin?
What? Me?
Since we have to go and arrange the site too,
we should take Joon Woo.
Joon Woo, you come with us.
What? I will.
I'll just go.
What good will Kim Hye Jin be there?
I should go even though I already have a lot on my plate.
Finally, my chance!
Jackpot Kim Joon Woo, I will definitely make you mine!
Where is the dryer?
Do you remember the puzzle from back then? It was also in the box.
Pu... zzle?
Ah, the peeping girl!
I was wondering why I had kept something like that but
once I started playing with the puzzle, I remembered doing it with you all the time.
I was thankful for it.
I'm here. I'll be up soon.
Hye Jin!
Oh, Seong Joon!
You've been waiting long?
Yeah. Let's go inside.
Hye Jin?
I found this.
Oh, this.
It's been a really long time, hasn't it?
I wasn't sure but when I looked for it, I still had it.
Isn't it amazing?
Right.
It's the piece from that time.
Who I knew from back then, that really was
you.
Omo, we meet at a place like this.
Did you come here for dinner?
Isn't that obvious? We're at a restaurant.
Now it seems you're even lying about your name to get a man.
Well, if you want to date more than one man,
I'm sure there are times a lie is necessary.
Is there anything else you're lying about beside your name?
I don't think it's any of your business.
I'm curious as to what kind of a man he is for you to be lying about your name.
Why don't you introduce me to him?
It's that..
there is a reason for it.
Pretend you didn't see me.
Why should I do that?
No matter what, aren't you the one who dates men for fun?
You being this way is a little
new.
I'm begging you.
Your voice was too low, so I couldn't hear you.
Can you say that again?
I'm begging you.
Please pretend you didn't see me.
Seong Joon, let's go.
What's the matter all of a sudden? Are you not feeling well?
Let's just get out quickly.
Hye Jin, seriously, what's wrong?
What's the matter?
You two really seem to suit each other.
Excuse me?
We'll meet again.
Call me later.
Hye Jin!
What's wrong? Who was that earlier?
Hye Jin.
That name...
Don't call me that.
Look at me. Huh?
First, look at my face.
Just stay like this for a minute.
Just for today.
Don't ask me anything.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Ugly Ducklings@Viki
You're late. Did you have a date somewhere again?
Yeah, something like that.
Did you eat? Should I make you something?
Of course I ate. Just look at the time.
Oh that's right, I thought your blanket was too thin so I changed it to a thicker one.
You did?
Thanks.
Hey, and what is that mess in your room?
I nearly called the police because I thought we were broken into. Clean up once in awhile.
Ahhh! The pretty ones only know how to take care of themselves.
They leave their room looking like a pig stye so a pig might mistake it for its house.
Who will marry that?
Let's sleep together.
What? You have a huge bed. Why?
Ah, this is nice.
Hey, must I sleep with that big body of yours?
I made it this small so you will let me sleep with you, right?
Hey, if you do that kind of a trick once more, I will...kill you!!!
Hey! Tickle, tickle!
Why? What is it?
What?
You have something to tell me.
Yeah.
I do.
I do, but...
Later.
I'll tell you everything later.
Hye Jin.
Until then,
can you wait a bit?
Are you going to be okay?
Being okay... is hard.
Ha Ri.
Oh, so nice.
Should I keep sleeping here from now on?
Dream on. Who said I'll let you sleep here?
I'm not sure what's going on, but...
don't wander around too long.
Okay.
Okay, Hye Jin.
You came?
Business travel team, let's meet on the first floor at 10 o'clock.
Yes!
Buongiorno! (Good morning)
Hello.
♫  Caro mio bene  ♫
Come in, come in.
What brings you here?
Ah, Director Cha asked me to get these signed off for her.
Cosa. What is it?
But..
how long do I have to wait for you to become The Most-like?
What? Ah.
I've been making an effort.
Oh, Mamma.
Troppo complicato! Troppo complicato! (Too complicated!)
This style is absurd and hopeless.
I'm sorry.
Omo, I feel nauseated. Again, I feel queasy.
See? I keep feeling nauseous.
Please be The Most-like, with some sense of style. Okay?
The Most-like, with a sense of style.
Everything!
Even signing something like this,
The Most-like.
Like how?
- The Most-like.  - Right.
Get out.
It hurts so much.
It's okay, it's okay.
The Most-like.
Fine. I will use it today.
What did I do?
I, Kim Hye Jin, promise to comply with Kim Shin Hyeok's request three times, no matter what.
Did you record that?
Of course I did. In case you denied it.
I was going to ask you for more but I am naturally very gentle and soft-hearted.
I decided to go easy on you for our first time.
Buy tonight's dinner. Make it whelk.
But add some plain noodles to it.
Okay well, whelk is easy enough.
Yes! Whelk!
Yes, i'll check on that.
Yes.
I'm going crazy.
- Hye Jin.- Yes?
I'm sorry but you'll have to go on the business trip instead of me.
What?
James Taylor's people called about the dress we're collaborating on
and they're sending the first draft of it in a few minutes.
I think I'll have to check it out and call them back.
Hurry up and head down.
Everyone should be waiting there since they have to leave soon.
But, I didn't pack a bag.
For now, take my luggage.
Everything you need to change into and sleep in, there's enough for one night.
But, still...
Hurry! They are all waiting.
Move! Move!
Ah, I'll be leaving.
Oh, my bag.
Goodbye. I'll be leaving.
Hye Jin, take care!
Jackson! Whelk!
Kim Joon Woo!
What's that car?
Let's you and I drive there together.
Didn't we decide to go together in Deputy Chief Editor's car?
He said he'd be right out.
Well, there's a lot luggage and it's easier this way for traveling a long distance.
I already told the Deputy Chief Editor and Sunbae Joo Yeong.
Hurry, get in.
I didn't hear about traveling separately.
Ah, I told you that's what we decided to do.
What are you doing?
You should have your seatbelt on.
Oh, Kim Joon Woo, what are you thinking?
Oh, Kim Joon Woo, what's with you?
No, nothing's up. I'm not thinking about anything.
Where did they go?
Director Cha has to take care of something urgent so
she can't go on this trip and she told me to go instead.
Oh.
There's a piece of thread..
Ah, that's okay.
I'll do it.
What? What does the text say?
Deputy Chief Editor, Joon Woo and I have something to take care of so we'll leave a little later.
Go on ahead with Sunbae Joo Yeong.
Then...
Let's get going.
What the? Ji Seong Joon and me are going alone?
Omo, what am I going to do?!
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Ugly Ducklings@Viki
She Was PrettyPreview
Business trip?
Who with?
Ji Seong Joon!
The seaaa~!
Then Jackson and the Deputy Chief Director are alone?
Joon Woo, look at the stars.
Deputy Chief Editor.
Right now, I am going to tell you something that you might be shocked to hear.
What are you saying right now?
Truthfully, I...